Look how cute they are!
Blush designs are popular for spring nails this year!
This year, we recommend the following spring nail designs
A design with a soft blush-like color in the center of the nail.
And then add lame or rhinestones to the blush part.
or add rhinestones.
You can enjoy various designs.
At Shibuya Loft
Recommended blush-like color design
There is an item that allows you to easily create popular blush designs.
These nail tips are very popular in Korea.
It's an easy-to-use sticker type with a slight pink hue, so you can easily create blush designs just by sticking it on your nails.
You can easily create blush nail designs just by sticking them on your nails!
Moreover, they use a magnetic gel that glows like water depending on the angle.
There are 40 tips in the package, so you can find the size that suits you best.
We are very happy that you can easily create authentic blush designs on your own!
Today, check out the new nail polish items that can be used through the summer!
Shibuya Loft has about 850 kinds of nail items!
Items that make it easier to remove gel nail polish, nail polish with gel nail polish ingredients, and more!
Among them, there is a new nail polish item that is on sale at the Loft!
That's the Edge-You nail sticker. The point is
The point is that they are plump!
Very plump!
So to speak, it's thick.
Even though they are stickers, they are plump and cute!
The stickers have six layers from the base to the top, so you can recreate the plumpness of gel nails.
Just peel it off from the sheet and stick it on your nails.
Just peel it off from the sheet and stick it on your nail.
After that, you can adjust the shape to your liking.
You can get a plump, shiny, salon-grade finish.
Using the included wood stick, it is very easy to peel off.
It's great that it's easy to do with stickers and has a glossy finish!
Next, the half cane!
There are about 170 kinds of new nail polishes alone!
There are gel nail stickers that harden naturally just by putting them on, and stick-type nails that are easy to apply.
There are also stick-type nails that are easy to apply.
Among them, I recommend the newest one.
The new color of Tone Drop! This is a new color of Tone Drop!
The popular Tone Drop, which sells out every time a new color is released
A shimmering champagne gold is now available!
It contains ultra-fine magnetic pearls.
So when you put the included magnetic stick close to it
the magnetic pearls are attracted to the stick.
You can put a line in the middle or
You can put a line in the middle or gather lame at the base.
You can enjoy various designs.
Depending on the position of the pearls, they shine in various ways, making them very fashionable.
Which nails will you be wearing this spring?
Please subscribe to our channel!